<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Android-With-Kotlin</string>
    <string name="web">WEB</string>
    <string name="camera">CAMERA</string>
    ♠
    <string name="news_contant">External Affairs Minister S. Jaishankar has warned that global trade calculations are being disrupted by increasing "tariff volatility", referencing broader shifts in the geopolitical
    and economic landscape.
    \n

    Speaking at the first Aravali Summit, hosted by Jawaharlal Nehru University\'s School of International Studies on its 70th anniversary, Jaishankar highlighted the strategic consequences of recent transformations, particularly the concentration of one-third of global manufacturing in a single geography—an apparent reference to China—and its impact on global supply chains. He noted the growing anti-globalisation sentiment in various societies and pointed to the instability caused by tariff changes,subtly referring to Washington\'s trade policies. Tensions between India and the US have recently escalated, especially after President Donald Trump doubled tariffs on Indian goods, including a 25 per cent additional duty on India’s imports of Russian crude oil.Jaishankar also outlined the significant shifts in the global energy landscape, with the US emerging as a major fossil fuel exporter and China dominating the renewable energy sector. He stressed that emerging models for managing data and artificial intelligence are increasingly competing with one another. Furthermore, he observed that Big Tech now plays a powerful, independent role on the world stage, new strategic connectivity routes are taking shape, and global mobility debates are grappling with the balance between skills demand and societal response.

In finance, he pointed to the growing influence of sanctions, asset seizures, and cryptocurrencies as redefining global financial norms. He also highlighted the intense competition for rare earths and critical minerals, which is being compounded by increasingly strict technology controls. According to Jaishankar, the nature of warfare is evolving, becoming more remote, technologically driven, and risk-laden.

Another area of concern, he noted, is the erosion of national sovereignty, facilitated by deep technological penetration and manipulation. Global rules and institutions are being re-evaluated, and in some cases, abandoned altogether. Jaishankar emphasized that cost is no longer the sole factor in economic decisions—issues of ownership and security are now equally critical. He warned of rising “end-to-end” risks, from concentrated production and narrow supply chains to market dependency. As the belief in balanced power erodes, he noted a shift towards actions driven by margins of power. Overall, Jaishankar concluded that the world is experiencing increased competition and fewer cooperative agreements, with global dynamics moving away from collaboration and more towards intersecting, often conflicting, interests.</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <!-- Strings related to login -->
    <string name="prompt_email">Email</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in">Sign in or register</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Sign in</string>
    <string name="welcome">"Welcome!"</string>
    <string name="invalid_username">Not a valid username</string>
    <string name="invalid_password">Password must be >5 characters</string>
    <string name="login_failed">"Login failed"</string>
</resources>